

github.com/stefanovallarella

in linkedin/in/stefanovallarella

stefanovallarella.com.ar

About me

I'm a Semi Senior Full Stack Developer, passionate about technology, with more than two and a half years of experience working with applications and websites using modern frameworks such as VueJS, ReactJS, NuxtJS.

If there's something I've learnt from my experience is that team work is the right way to achieve quality learning and continuous improvement.

I worked at EducacionIT for a few years, and my role was to develop and maintain the company's applications and products using VueJS, NuxtJS, JS, Typescript, Docker, AWS. Also I participated in new challenges in order to improve my back-end knowledge by building REST APIs in Node.js / Typescript / Sequelize.

At the moment I'm working at Navent, as a Full Stack Developer, developing Android Native Mobile apps in Kotlin.

Work Experience

Full Stack developer at Navent Dec 2022 — present

 Development and maintenance of company's own android native mobile applications built in Kotlin.

STACK: Android Studio / Kotlin / MVVM

Full Stack developer at EducaciónIT Aug 2022 — Dec 2022

• Development of public and private APIs to be used by company's own products. Usage of Node.js, Typescript, Sequelize.

STACK: NodeJS / TypeScript / SQL / Sequelize

Front End developer at EducaciónIT Jan 2021 — Aug 2022

- Development and maintenance of company's own applications and products built in Vuejs / Nuxtjs / Typescript. .
- Development and maintenance of dynamic applications (PDF's, Certificates) built in JS, Vite, Puppeteer, CSS3, HTML5.
- I've had comprehensive participation in the analysis, brain storming, thinking and rethinking the development of applications and products along with the Design area, UX team and management.

STACK: Vue JS / Nuxt JS / Tailwind / PostCSS / Vite

Front End developer at Onlines&co Dec 2019 — Jan 2021

• Layout of different projects in HTML, CSS, SASS/SCSS. Usage of Javascript / Jquery.

STACK: HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / jQuery

Education

OOAD - Object Oriented Paradigm Introduction EducaciónIT (2021)

Design Patterns EducaciónIT (2021)

Full Stack Node.js Course Digital House (2020)

Udemy courses React JS, Android in Kotlin

Technical skills

Frontend

Vue JS, Nuxt JS, React JS, Redux JavaScript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, PostCSS, Android Studio, Kotlin.

Backend

API Rest, Node JS, Express, MySQL, Sequelize, AWS (CloudWatch, S3)

Others

Git, GitHub, Docker, Npm, Yarn, Webpack, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, Miro, Trello, Jira, Scrum, Scrumban.

Soft skills

Communication and active listening, teamwork, leadership, planning and time management, flexibility, problem solving, critical thinking and responsibility.

Languages

Spanish

Native proficiency

English

Advanced (reading, speaking, writing)